// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "It is an active process of constructing meaning.",
    answer: "Reading",
    options: [
      "Relevance",
      "Reading",
      "Information",
      "Context"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "It is simply means worthiness; quality of being suitable or having some kind of value.",
    answer: "Relevance",
    options: [
      "Relevance",
      "Performance",
      "Information",
      "Value"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "These are the thoughts that are expressed around us through the different materials we encountered. ",
    answer: "Ideas",
    options: [
      "Thoughts",
      "Ideas",
      "Materials",
      "Literature"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "It empowers the reader to judge the relevance and worth of ideas to his/her reading goals.",
    answer: "Knowledge",
    options: [
      "Dreams",
      "Power",
      "Goals",
      "Knowledge"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " We should remember the following when judging the relevance and worth of ideas of the materials presented Except:",
    answer: "Listen to gossip",
    options: [
      "Note important information",
      "Listen to gossip",
      "Check the organization andclariffyof ideas",
      "Gather Evidence"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "It’s a statement that presents an arguable position. It mirrors your interpretation, belief or opinion.",
    answer: "Claim",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Argument",
      "Bias",
      "Evidence"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "It is the strongest argument against your claim.",
    answer: "Counterclaim",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Argument",
      "Evidence",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "It backups your arguments and serve as your reference.",
    answer: "Evidence",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Argument",
      "Evidence",
      "Prejudice"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "It means the quality of being based on valid reasons, good judgement or reasoning.",
    answer: "Soundness",
    options: [
      "Evidence",
      "Soundness",
      "Texts",
      "Reason"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How does the author help up believe his/her statement?",
    answer: "Evidence",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What does the author want the reader to believe?",
    answer: "Claim",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 12,
    question: "Is the supporting evidence strong enough to support the author’s main idea or beliefs?",
    answer: "Reason",
    options: [
      "Claim",
      "Evidence",
      "Reason",
      "Counterclaim"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 13,
    question: "It is the characteristics of a sound reasoning Except:",
    answer: "Counterclaim",
    options: [
      "Quality of data",
      "Existenceof supporting details",
      "Counterclaim",
      "Relevance of addition data"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Is a statement that can be verified.",
    answer: "fact",
    options: [
      "Opinion",
      "Evidence",
      "Reasoning",
      "fact"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Is a view or judgement formed about something, not necessarily based on fact or knowledge.",
    answer: "Opinion",
    options: [
      "Opinion",
      "Evidence",
      "Reasoning",
      "Fact"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Is the capacity of producing desired output that can showcase a clear impression.",
    answer: "Efectiveness",
    options: [
      "Reading",
      "Speaking",
      "Output",
      "Efectiveness"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 17,
    question: "Refers to the condition or quality of being adequate or sufficient.",
    answer: "Sufficiency",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 18,
    question: "Refers to the conformity to truth or to a standard or model.",
    answer: "Accuracy",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Refers to the attractiveness or the state of wanting to know or learn about something or someone.",
    answer: "Appeal",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Refers to the facts provided or learned about something or someone.",
    answer: "Information",
    options: [
      "Information",
      "Appeal",
      "Accuracy",
      "Sufficiency",
    ]
  },
  // you can make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];